<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Infinite Scroll Example</string>


    <!-- Title string array -->
    <string-array name="title">
        <item>Madrid</item>
        <item>Barcelona</item>
        <item>Valencia</item>
        <item>Sevilla</item>
        <item>Zaragoza</item>
        <item>Málaga</item>
        <item>Murcia</item>
        <item>Bilbao</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Location string array -->
    <string-array name="location">
        <item>Comunidad de Madrid</item>
        <item>Cataluña</item>
        <item>Comunidad Valenciana</item>
        <item>Andalucía</item>
        <item>Aragón</item>
        <item>Andalucía</item>
        <item>Murcia</item>
        <item>País Vasco</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Year string array -->
    <string-array name="description">
        <item>Madrid is a south-western European city, the capital of Spain, and the largest municipality of the Community of Madrid.
            The population of the city is almost 3.2 million with a metropolitan area population of approximately 6.5 million.
            It is the third-largest city in the European Union, after London and Berlin, and its metropolitan area is the third-largest in the European Union after London and Paris.
            The city spans a total of 604.3 km2 \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
        <item>Barcelona is the capital city of the autonomous community of Catalonia in Spain and Spain\'s second most populated city,
            with a population of 1.6 million within its administrative limits. Its urban area extends beyond the administrative city
            limits with a population of around 4.7 million people, being the seventh-most populous urban area in the European Union after
            Paris, London, Madrid, the Ruhr area, Berlin and Milan. It is the largest metropolis on the Mediterranean Sea,
            located on the coast between the mouths of the rivers Llobregat and Besòs,
            and bounded to the west by the Serra de Collserola mountain range, the tallest peak of which is 512 metres (1,680 ft) high.
            \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
        <item>Valencia, is the capital of the autonomous community of Valencia and the third largest city in Spain after Madrid and Barcelona,
            with around 800,000 inhabitants in the administrative centre. Its urban area extends beyond the administrative city limits with a population of around 1.5 million people.
            Valencia is Spain\'s third largest metropolitan area, with a population ranging from 1.7 to 2.5 million.
            The Port of Valencia is the 5th busiest container port in Europe and the busiest container port on the Mediterranean Sea.
            The city is ranked at Gamma in the Globalization and World Cities Research Network.
         \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
        <item>Seville is the capital and largest city of the autonomous community of Andalusia and the province of Seville, Spain.
            It is situated on the plain of the River Guadalquivir. The inhabitants of the city are known as sevillanos (feminine form: sevillanas) or hispalenses,
            after the Roman name of the city, Hispalis. Seville has a municipal population of about 703,000 as of 2011, and a metropolitan population of about 1.5 million,
            making it the fourth-largest city in Spain and the 30th most populous municipality in the European Union.
            Its Old Town, the third largest in Europe with an area of 4 square kilometres (2 sq mi),
            contains three UNESCO World Heritage Sites: the Alcázar palace complex, the Cathedral and the General Archive of the Indies.
            The Seville harbour, located about 80 kilometres (50 miles) from the Atlantic Ocean, is the only river port in Spain. Seville is also the hottest major metropolitan area in Europe,
            with summer average high temperatures of above 35 °C.
        \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
        <item>Zaragoza, also called Saragossa in English,
            is the capital city of the Zaragoza province and of the autonomous community of Aragon, Spain.
            It lies by the Ebro river and its tributaries, the Huerva and the Gállego,
            roughly in the center of both Aragon and the Ebro basin.
        \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
        <item>Málaga is a municipality, capital of the Province of Málaga,
            in the Autonomous Community of Andalusia, Spain. With a population of 568,479 in 2013,
            it is the second most populous city of Andalusia and the sixth largest in Spain.
            The southernmost large city in Europe, it lies on the Costa del Sol (Coast of the Sun) of the Mediterranean,
            about 100 km (62.14 mi) east of the Strait of Gibraltar and about 130 km (80.78 mi) north of Africa.
         \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
        <item>Murcia is a city in south-eastern Spain, the capital and most populous city of the Autonomous Community of the Region of Murcia,
            and the seventh largest city in the country, with a population of 442,573 inhabitants in 2009 (about one third of the total population of the Region).
            The population of the metropolitan area was 689,591 in 2010. It is located on the Segura River,
            in the Southeast of the Iberian Peninsula, noted by a climate with hot summers, mild winters, and relatively low precipitation.
        \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
        <item>Bilbao is a municipality and city in Spain, a major city in the province of Biscay in the autonomous community of the Basque Country.
            It is the largest municipality of the Basque Country and the tenth largest in Spain,
            with a population of 353,187 in 2010.The Bilbao metropolitan area has roughly 1 million inhabitants,
            making it one of the most populous metropolitan areas in northern Spain; with a population of 875,552 the comarca of Greater
            Bilbao is the fifth-largest urban area in Spain. Bilbao is also the main urban area in what is defined as the Greater Basque region.
            \n Source: Wikipedia</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_tabbed">Infinite Scroll Example</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>


</resources>